http://www.cryoport.com/privacy-policy

Science. Logistics. Certainty.
About Us
Partners (CUE)
Privacy Policy
Cryoport Systems, LLC Website Privacy Statement.
This Privacy Policy Statement applies to all visitors who register on the Cryoport Systems, LLC website, www.cryoport.com.
The Information We Collect
The personal information we collect when you register on our website can be provided by you for several different reasons which are described below:
You may need to register to receive certain information or to download certain documents.
You may opt to provide us information about yourself if you are interested in an employment opportunity at Cryoport Systems, LLC. The information requested from you will be based on your area of interest.
You can register to receive customized information. This information is generally collected on "Contact Us" or download request forms where you can request information. The personal information you provide on these forms may include your name, title, company name, address, contact telephone numbers, and email address, and in certain cases your areas of professional interest. The type of information that you may download after providing your information includes: video / audio archives, literature, articles, white papers, and case studies.
You can choose to register to receive access to webcasts, periodic newsletters, or information on a specific product or service. Generally, the personal information collected when you register to receive this type of information is your name, company, affiliation, and email address.
The Way We Use InformationWe store the information you provide about yourself in a secure database in order to provide you with the information, products, and/or services you request. The information is stored for the lifetime of the database unless you request that it be removed. The information you provide us about yourself will be shared with Cryoport Systems, LLC employees to the extent necessary to accommodate your request. You must consent for us to share your identifiable information with third parties, who would be bound by a confidentiality agreement.
For example, if you provide your name, mailing address, telephone and email address and request more information about Cryoport Systems, LLC services, such information may be shared with third parties with whom we work, affiliates, vendors, or regulatory agencies, but your information will always be protected under the terms of this Privacy Policy Statement.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information about the use of our website to improve the navigation, content, and design of our site. This information may include, for example, the most and least requested pages and the number of users from the U.S. and other countries, among other things.
Finally, unless otherwise accepted below, we would not use your personal information provided to us online for purposes other than those you requested without also providing you an opportunity to agree or otherwise limit such unrelated purposes.
ExceptionsExcept as described above, we will not otherwise use or disclose any of your personal information, except to the extent reasonably necessary: (i) to correct technical problems and malfunctions and to technically process your information; (ii) to protect the security and integrity of our website; (iii) to protect our rights and property and the rights and property of others; (iv) to take precautions against liability; (v) to the extent required by law or to respond to judicial process; or (vii) to the extent permitted under other provisions of law, to provide information to law enforcement agencies or for an investigation on a matter related to public safety, as applicable.
Our Commitment to Data SecurityThe personal information your provide is stored in a secure electronic database that has access limited to only those who need to know your information in order to address your requests. Our computer systems have physical, electronic and supervisory procedures in place to help protect that your information is not altered in any way without your authorization. Cryoport Systems, LLC also has a corporate policy in place that requires all personnel not to disclose personal information to any third party that is not entitled to have that information.
CookiesA cookie is a piece of data stored on the hard drive of your computer. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personal information while on our site. Cryoport Systems, LLC uses cookies on our website in order (a) to allow site visitors to personalize their experience by accessing information, products, and services relevant to their areas of interest, (b) to track a user session within a subscribed product, and (c) to allow site visitors to vote only once in periodic opinion polls.
We receive IP addresses in the normal course of the operation of our website. An IP address is a number assigned to you by your Internet service provider so you can access the Internet. Although we do receive IP addresses, we do not use them to identify you personally or disclose them to others.
Our Commitment to Children's PrivacyProtecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we do not collect or maintain information at our website from those we know are under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
How You Can Access or Correct Your InformationYou may update or remove the information you provided to us by contacting us - see Contact Us on the Cryoport Systems, LLC website, or the section below on “How to Contact Cryoport Systems, LLC” To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before updating or removing your information. The information you provide us may be archived or stored periodically by us according to backup processes conducted in the ordinary course of business. Information stored as part of this backup process will be deleted in due course on a regular schedule.
Links to Other WebsitesOur website may contain links to other websites. You should carefully review the privacy policies and practices of other websites, as we cannot control or be responsible for their privacy practices.
Notice on How We Will Use Your InformationCryoport Systems, LLC collects personal information directly from the individuals, so you will be informed about the purpose for which the information is collected and if there is an intent to provide that information to a third party. You will also be notified if there is intent to use the information for purposes other than those originally disclosed. This notice will be provided in a clear and conspicuous language before such personal information will be used for purposes other than that for which it was originally collected or processed.
Your Privacy ChoicesCryoport Systems, LLC will offer you the opportunity to choose (opt out) whether your personal information is to be disclosed to a third party or is to be used for a purpose that is incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized.
For sensitive information, Cryoport Systems, LLC will give you the opportunity for an explicit affirmative choice (opt in) to have your information disclosed to a third party or used for purpose(s) other than those for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized.
Sensitive information is personal information specifying medical or health conditions, racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership, or information specifying the sexual orientation of the individual.
Transferring Your Information to a Third PartyCryoport Systems, LLC may provide your information to third parties such as affiliates, vendors, or to regulatory agencies, but your information will always be protected under the terms of this Privacy Policy Statement. This will be achieved by first ascertaining that the third party will provide the same level of privacy protection as described in this Privacy Policy Statement. If it becomes known that a third party organization that has received personal information is using or disclosing it a manner contrary to this Statement, Cryoport Systems, LLC will take reasonable steps to prevent or stop this use or disclosure.
How Your Information Is Secured
Privacy PolicyCryoport Systems, LLC employs reasonable precautions to prevent your personal information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. We also take reasonable steps to ensure your information is reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete and current. This is achieved by storing your information in a secure electronic database that is a component of a computer system that has physical, electronic, and supervisory procedures in place to ensure compliance with all electronic records regulations.
How You Can Access and Correct Your InformationYou may access your personal information to revise or delete it, if it is inaccurate, except where the rights of other persons would be violated. Access can be obtained by contacting Cryoport Systems, LLC as shown below.
How this Privacy Policy Statement Is EnforcedCryoport Systems, LLC's Privacy Officer has put into place self-assessment procedures to ensure compliance with this Statement. These procedures will be exercised on a random basis, and any employee who is found to intentionally violate this Privacy Policy Statement will be subject to disciplinary action up to and including termination of employment.
How Your Dispute or Complaint May Be ResolvedAny questions, concerns or complaints regarding the use of your personal information should be directed to the Cryoport Systems, LLC Privacy Officer using the contact information presented below. Cryoport Systems, LLC will attempt to resolve any dispute or complaint relating to the misuse or improper disclosure of personal information by investigating it in accordance with the principles contained in this Privacy Policy Statement. Appropriate corrective and preventive action will be implemented and follow-up on such action will be conducted to verify that the expressed concern or complaint has been resolved.
How to Contact Cryoport Systems, LLC Regarding Privacy IssuesQuestions, concerns, or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy Statement or the handling of your personal information should be submitted to
Privacy OfficerCryoport Systems, LLC17305 Daimler St.Irvine, CA 92614
You may also contact the Cryoport Systems, LLC Privacy Officer at the following email address: ir@cryoport.com
Changes to This Privacy Policy StatementThis Privacy Policy Statement may be amended from time to time to ensure consistency and compliance with changes in the privacy legislation or in statutory requirements. Changes to this policy will be posted on the Cryoport Systems, LLC website and we recommend that you review this Privacy Policy Statement to ensure you are aware of any changes made to it.
Effective DateThis Privacy Policy Statement became effective on: March 1, 2016.
What our clients are saying
“Cryoport does an amazing job of handling the shipping and logistics for transporting cryopreserved materials. We have switched to them for all of our exports.”
Bioengineering Core Employee – Cryoport Customer
“As a customer I'm very pleased with the service I received from Cryoport. Cryoport’s team always answered my questions, provided help in a professional manner and were extremely attentive.”
Cryoport Customer
“Had I known how great Cryoport’s dry vapor shipper and logistics system worked, we would have used Cryoport for all our previous shipments to the U.S. In the past we have used dry ice and several times we lost valuable cells because our shipments would sit in customs forever and the dry ice would evaporate. Cryoport eliminated that concern altogether. I will certainly be utilizing Cryoport’s services for future shipments.”
Principal Investigator – Cryoport Customer
“By using Cryoport I experienced much less stress as my shipment went through customs!”
Principal Investigator – Cryoport Customer
“I called Cryoport after hours for information about a shipment I needed to schedule and received absolutely outstanding customer service. Cryoport provided me with a lot of helpful information and great advice. It's rare and refreshing to receive such great service.”
Cryoport Customer
“Not only did my cells arrive safely, Cryoport’s service was professional and efficient. I highly recommend Cryoport.”
Hematologist – Cryoport Customer
“Working with Cryoport was a truly remarkable difference compared to my experience with other shippers. With the previous shipping company I was working with, it took almost three months to establish a ‘deep frozen account’ and required numerous hoop-jumping shenanigans only to ultimately be informed that the company could not arrange a shipment to or from Israel, which they were informed from the start was our desired shipping source.
Our sales rep at this organization was as dumbfounded by our experience as we were. To his credit, after his company declined our business, he suggested I contact Cryoport. I have written thanking him for his suggestion and to let his ‘powers-that-be’ know how different my experiences were.”
Cryoport Biopharma Customer
“When compared to other shippers, I am highly satisfied with Cryoport’s pricing and service.”
Lab Manager – Cryoport Customer
“Our organization is more than impressed by our experience with Cryoport. We feel confident our material is being well-managed throughout transit. Cryoport provides extraordinary customer service and continuously they not only meet, but exceed our expectations. Late yesterday afternoon Cryoport worked tirelessly to coordinate a shipment to Japan and today seemed to effortlessly manage a late-day return. It is a pleasure working with Cryoport.”
Senior Supply Chain Analyst – Cryoport Customer
“Cryoport’s service is easy, straightforward and very convenient. We used to run into issues with transporting specimens to outside labs and Cryoport has eliminated this hurdle. Knowing Cryoport has it handled helps me sleep at night.”
Professor of Anatomy, Histology and Cell Biology – Cryoport Customer
“I'd like to commend Cryoport for their fantastic service. Our collaborator was also similarly impressed and will be recommending Cryoport to her colleagues. In addition to the great service and quality product, Cryoport’s pricing is second to none. We look forward to working with Cryoport for all of our future temperature-sensitive shipments."
Lab Manager – Cryoport Customer
"I want to thank everyone at Cryoport who was involved in the rapid recovery of the missing Cryoport shipper containing a patient’s tumor tissue. By promptly locating the shipper and recharging it while in transit, the patient was able to receive the vaccine manufactured from this tissue on time. We are so very appreciative of Cryoport’s customer service. Without the services that Cryoport provides, our clinical trials would not be available to patients."
Director of Clinical Operations — Cryoport Customer
“Cryoport provides a reliable solution to ship temperature-sensitive biologics around the world. The Cryoport solution is easy for scientists to use. They respond quickly, have great customer service and anticipate problems. I am able to speak to someone 24/7 who is an expert on MY package. It is personal service focused on deep frozen life sciences. I consider Cryoport to be an extended member of my team.”
Product Operations Specialist – Cryoport Customer
Contact us or request a quote.
Americas • EMEA • APACSales • +1 949.232.1900
|
Support • +1 949.470.2300
©2020 Cryoport Systems, LLC. All rights reserved.
Partners (CUE)
The first shippers certified for the delivery of human advanced therapies.
See How We Are Setting the Standard
COVID-19 Update
